BGM
Here we go... up-cam, this time with student Eguchi from BEYONES Subway.
This is Fukuda Marin from Tsubaki Factory.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at our two MCs.
I, Eguchi...
I, Eguchi, would like to talk about the new start of BEYONDZ as a 10-member band.
With the change in the number of members, there were some changes in the song assignments, and also some modifications in the bites.
We are now in the stage of changing the roles of BEYONDZ, and we are all trying to cope with the changes.
We've sung many songs and the members haven't changed at all, but suddenly we've become a resident group and there have been changes in song assignments and also in the way the double values are ticked.
The numbering of the bamilli and the numbering of the numbers has also changed.
If the number of performers was reduced or if one of the performers disappeared, the content of the story would change.
So we changed the story completely or changed it to a completely different story.
Everyone is trying their best with a positive attitude to make a new effort, so it's a different story for everyone.
I think everyone watching the show will be able to enjoy a different kind of change in the Beyonce's.
When the organization changes, there are a lot of changes.
We have a lot of changes with new members and so on, so I want to do my best.
I will do my best.
As for me, Fukuda
Yumi Kasai, including myself, Ayuori Yagi, myself, and Yumi Fukuda.
I would like to talk about the live event held on August 5 with four of my classmates, including myself, Yumi Kasai, Ayuori Yagi, myself and Runo Yofu.
It was the first time I was entrusted with the responsibility of choreographing the last song, which was the climax of the event.
I was entrusted with the responsibility of the last song, which is the climax of the show, but I made a mistake because I used ambiguous words.
So the staff was not sure if it was okay to play the song or not.
So there was a mysterious time.
At that time, I thought my words might not have been heard.
When I said it one last time, the sound flowed together at that timing.
I had an experience the other day that I was really upset.
I'm still a junior member of Tsubaki Factory.
So the older members often do the MC for us.
Now that new members have joined the group, I feel I have to do better.
It was a happening that made me realize that I have to be stronger and stronger.
Suddenly, when my role came to me
I am filled with gratitude for those who have always been there for me, but I also want to do my best to grow even more.
I would like to do my best to grow even more.
Now, let's start with this time's Up-Kami, here.
The making of Tsubaki Factory's music video for "Seishun Exabyte
Tsubaki Factory's latest single will be released on August 28th.
Tsubaki Factory's latest single
Please take a look at the making of the music video for the song "Seishun Exabyte" from Tsubaki Factory's latest single to be released on August 28th!
Thank you for watching!
The setup is that I'm filming the three of them with this lens on this camera with this reflection.
Lip.
So what you all see is with this lens.
Shot with this lens.
There's more than one way to read that.
It's also absurdly good to read it properly.
Maybe it's a place I can't repeat.
We're shooting a music video for a new song!
This is Kisora Shinnuma's last music video shoot.
Kisora Shinnuma is wearing an outfit with lots of light blue, her member color!
I think it's going to be a very fresh and spring-like music video!
I'm really looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to the completion!
I'll do my best for the shoot!
The two of us on both sides are a little too close to each other.
I thought we were a little too close to each other, like our shoulders and faces were butted up against each other...
Finally on the mirror!
More and more
Here
Like this.
Here you go
Okay, let's do it like this.
Close up, close up, close up, close up.
This time, it's another group rip, amidst the larger storyline of Shinnuma-san dropping his phone in the pool and everyone picking it up.
Yes, it's a bit free.
Oh, what's that?
The camera.
All automatic.
Congratulations!
Does it say that over here?
It says "I love you.
Oda-san, Oda-san, let me see it.
Yes, we're going to go 10 seconds left.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Okay, that's good.
Okay, next.
Okay, let's go.
And since the cookie team is on the screen, we're going to keep the atmosphere of the three of you having a nice conversation.
I'm going to make it look like the three of you are having a nice conversation the whole time.
Oh, man, it's still hard.
Okay, okay, okay.
Ten seconds left!
Okay, okay, okay! Yes, yes, yes!
I hope the goat is hungry to cook.
Okay, let's do it!
Yes! Let's get started!
What are you doing?
Putting in the pasta.
The goat made it!
What is it, King?
The jungle!
It's always a sight to see.
Cute!
Yes, cut!
Yes, OK!
Okay, everyone, please roll the camera in human-powered stop motion.
Here we go!
Okay, let's start!
Shin Mizuno!
Yo!
Oh, look!
Yeah!
Ooh!
Yes!
Yes, cut!
Ready.
Ready? - Yeah.
Three, two, one, start.
And now...
We're filming the kitch scene.
And I was...
I was holding the pasta.
I put a lot of pressure on it.
I accidentally...
I broke it.
I was filming.
It was so difficult.
That part is supposed to be used as a slow-motion
I heard that they are going to use it in slow motion.
but the moment he breaks it...
I close my eyes.
It's a human instinct.
So...
No...
So it was a little difficult not to close my eyes at the moment of folding.
So the director told me to keep my eyes closed.
And that's how we shot it...
Let's make it look like Mr. Goat and Mr. Kasai are filming and filming.
I said, "Take a picture, take a picture, take a picture!
Mr. Shinnuma came up to me and said
Oh, my God!
Oh!
There's one where the camera was getting closer earlier, so can I ask you to get closer?
Three, two, one
Yes!
Talk in three, two, one.
Okay, I'm gonna bone up now.
Three, two, one.
I'm only a little involved.
Yes, please.
Okay, let's go live.
Okay, here we go.
Three, two, one.
Hey, Pon-chan!
Wow!
Whoo!
Hey, Pon-chan!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Whoa!
Now...
We shot a scene where they were cooking,
We shot the scene where they were cooking, and I made them shoot various patterns of facial expressions,
That was very difficult, when I slowed it down with the surprised face,
If I slowed down the scene with a surprised face, the surprised face would not look the way I wanted it to,
So I had to keep in mind how to slow down the scene,
So, I had to keep in mind how to slow down the camera.
We had a lot of fun talking with each other after the shoot.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
I think that's enough.
Cut.
Three twenty-one.
Ahhh!
Come on, take it.
No, no, no.
Good NG
I'll just say there was a lot of turnover.
Go!
I'm just saying that's a good place to start.
No, no, no, no, I'm going to stop right here.
I'll join you and the ring.
Oh, I'm definitely in too many.
Next?
Next.
Yes, let's get it back.
Yes, let's go next.
Okay, let's get started.
321.
Oh, that's good, right?
Cut.
321.
Don.
321 Don!
Yes, sir!
321 bam!
Yes!
It's okay, it's okay!
I'm sorry! Again! Again!
One more!
Yes! Cut!
Yes!
Oh! That's great!
But it's funny!
That's great!
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
OK!
Kisarazu-chan's last music video shoot is over!
Yay!
How did you like it?
This new song is a music video with a great storyline.
We shot a lot of scenes with various members.
It's different from the previous music videos
I think it's going to be a nice and moving music video.
I'm really looking forward to the completion of the music video.
I'm really looking forward to the completion of this music video.
I'm really looking forward to the completion of the music video, and there were a lot of emotional scenes that we filmed.
I'm very excited to see how it will turn out.
I am very excited to see how the music video will turn out.
I've got a sparkling smile on my face.
I think you can see Kisora's sparkling smile
I think you can really see Kisora-chan's sparkling smile in this music video, so I think it's going to be a great piece.
I think it's going to be a great piece of work.
Also, the most exciting thing about shooting this music video
The thing that made me the happiest was
The most exciting part of the music video shoot was that we were able to finish the shoot together for the last time.
We were able to finish the shoot together.
I was very happy because we could finish the shoot together.
I was very happy.
I hope everyone will watch it a lot!
The title of the song "Seishun Exabyte" is quite unique.
I think the title of the song is quite unique.
The word "exabyte" is a word
The word "exabyte" is used to express the volume of data.
Memories with everyone...
I don't care about the amount of data.
It's not about the amount of data, it's about the amount of memories you have with everyone.
The song itself is quite cheerful.
The song itself is quite bright, but each lyric is very fragile.
but each lyric has a very fragile feeling
There are many parts that make me feel sad.
It's a song that gives me a sense of duality.
The last music video shoot with Mr. Shinnuma
I had a lot of fun shooting the music video with Mr. Shinnuma.
I thought the song was great from the first time I heard it live, and I really liked the refreshing tone of the song.
I watched the music video over and over again, and as the title says, it really conveys the spirit of the song and the refreshing feeling it has.
Also, there were a lot of happening scenes, and I was able to see a lot of surprised expressions on each member's face, which you don't usually see.
I was wondering how they filmed the happening scenes, so I'm glad that I was able to see the making of the film and see how it was filmed.
I'm glad I got to see the making of the film and see how it was filmed.
That's all for the making of Tsubaki Factory's music video for "Seishun Exabyte.
Tsubaki Factory's new single "Seishun Exabyte" will be released on August 28th.
Thanks to you, I can do my best
Here's the next one!
JuiceJuice Tokyo Bra Vocal Recording
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Rei Inoue's vocal from JuiceJuice's latest single, Tokyo Bra!
Well, let's go film it, shall we? Then let's go MFK.
I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you Side mirror town wavering
I don't love you, I don't love you, I love you, Tokyo, I'm going to overflow tonight
Yeah, well, if I had to guess, I'd say it's that one.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
If you do it in a way that's cooler...
Oh, yes...
You don't have to speak so loudly.
Yes
Yes, I love you.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I don't love you, I love you, I love you Tokyo, it's gonna overflow tonight
I'm going to overflow tonight.
Radio Curve, you're feeling it?
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
Let's do it.
I don't love you. I love you, Tokyo. I'm gonna overflow tonight.
Radio Curve, I'm gonna make it hot.
It's raining.
It's work, isn't it?
Why are you down?
I think I'll give it one more shot.
Patient... it's okay.
Yes, ma'am.
I don't love you.
I do love you.
Tokyo, it's going to overflow tonight.
Radio.
I love you!
Tomorrow
It's raining.
I know you're already at work, so why are you feeling down?
Yeah, okay, okay, I'm good.
Okay, come on back to the top.
Because you're a real boy who never learns.
Why are you so down?
Because you're a real boy who never learns
I can't leave him alone, he's so weak
A story of emotions
Time to get out of that next body
This one's good, but can you go up an octave with your back voice?
Hmmm...
I can't leave you alone, Bargain Acre
I can't leave you alone, Bargain Acres.
Yes, sir?
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
I'm sorry, when you say it like that, I'll take this later.
Later?
Sorry, sorry.
Just give me one more shot of what you're feeling right now.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Those days you gave me
I can't leave your phone alone, you weak girl
Silence for peace, no escape, breath holding breath
Then, the octave higher you were talking about a little while ago
Herb's advice that won't let me leave, the weak girl who can't be left alone
I'll have some of this.
Yes, sir.
You can't unravel it, go weak-kneed.
OK
Yes, let's try to rust it, is that OK?
Yes.
If you get the message, let's go. Or do you want me to give it to you in the middle? Either way is fine.
Oh, the middle one.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, let's take the passenger side down to the drop-off.
Emotional Story When you get out of that corner of the moon
Temptation Cheap Snow Ravenger Here you come home
Auburn Hand Sleepless Love.
Get out of the passenger seat
Get out of the passenger seat.
I mean, like, around the passenger seat.
Passenger seat.
I'm going to use a tool called "dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah.
Get out of the passenger seat.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, let's continue.
The story of emotions When you get out
At the gate of that moon
Temptation
The stranger's Ravenger
come to understand
The Reaction of Deprivation
Of Sleepless Love
Get Out of the Passenger Seat
OK.
Okay, I'm gonna go all the way up your ass from here, too.
Yes, sir.
Sleepless in love
Get out of the passenger seat.
Let's get out of the passenger seat
Let's go see a new morning
Graduation, the hair is getting soft in the back, the night wind
Oh, Kanji OK
Yes, Aichi, it's okay.
Yes, sir.
Please give me one self-patch.
Down the tree line of sleepless love
Let's go see a new morning with a new me
Graduation, rather than hair softening night wind
Well, I guess that's it then...
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
I thought Inoue-san's feminine yet strong core voice was perfect for this song, and her vibrato was very cool.
And her vibrato
It was really nice to listen to her vibrato.
It's hard for me to learn how to use vibrato.
It's difficult for me too, and I wonder how I can do the alma mater.
When I heard your recording
I thought your vibrato was very skillful and cool.
The song "Tokyo Blur" by JuiceJuice is a song
I feel like there are so many different developments in one song.
I have the impression that the atmosphere of the song changes many times within one song.
I've seen it at Hello Project concerts.
I've seen it at Hello Project concerts, and I think it's a very difficult song.
But the way Ms. Inoue sings it, changing the way she sings each part a little...
Personally, I thought your Japanese pronunciation sounded very stylish.
It was very comfortable to listen to, and I thought it was very nice.
I felt it was very nice.
That's all for JuiceJuice Tokyo puller Rei Inoue's vocal recording.
Thanks for watching after a long time!
This is Apkami with Saya Eguchi of BEYONDZ Subway and Marin Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory.
Next up is BEYONDZ Hi2Diamond Chorus Recording
From the latest BEYONDZ single
Here's a sneak peek at the chorus recording by Rika Shimakura and Kurumi Takase of Hi2Diamond.
Let's start with the B melody.
Let's start with the B-melody part using 1B.
Diamond Diamond Diamond Diamond You
and then the last part, Let's Shine Together
Let's Shine Together" is a very sharp Let's Shine Together
Let's Shine Together
Diamond Diamond Diamond You
Let's continue with the chorus part.
Let's continue with the chorus part. Let's dance, let's dance!
Let's dance, let's dance!
Let's dance!
Hight Diamonds!
And don't let the sound go down
Let's dance all day long
And also, let's dance all day long
I do diamond
There
goes the subtle sound of
music
Yes, I'll eat, the last one is
Just be yourself
Just be yourself".
Let's go!
Yes, sir.
Just be yourself
I want to start the second half of the song without hesitation.
Yes, I'll start from here.
Yes, I'll take it. That's all for now. Thank you for your time.
Hello, good morning. Please.
First of all, I would like to use 1B to put in diamonds.
Yes, sir.
Diamonds, diamonds, diamonds, diamonds, diamonds, diamonds, diamonds, diamonds, diamonds, diamonds.
Let's shine together
OK, I'll take it!
Now let's go to 2A.
Let's go to Mr. Takase's part.
Takase-san's part
Okay, Gaia, let's go. First of all, after the first chorus at the top of the door, it sounds like "Ginga to ginga," and then "Hey, hey, foo foo" part.
Yes, OK.
This is the part where we want to create a rather mischievous party atmosphere.
Higher, yes.
I wanted to have a higher tension and higher pitch in the voice.
I want to have one more.
Then, please guess.
Please guess.
Yes, I'll take it.
Gaia goes to Gaia for the rap part.
We'll let the wrap flow. And in between, I'll put Hey.
It's the very end.
Hey! Hey! Foo!
This is a new addition, but it's a little longer.
I just added a new one, but it's a little longer.
It's like a paper tape that goes whooshing forward.
It's like a parabolic Foo!
Still ciao Turbod
Then the last one. More rough and tumble. I don't know what will happen if I do more.
Rough and tumble.
Yes, I'll give it a try.
Please give it a try. Please do.
It's a little rough.
Is it right?
Yes, it is. As you requested.
So, I got it.
Yes!
That's all for Team C.
It's over!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
This song has so many chorus parts, and the chorus part has 4 voices,
That's right. I had to adjust the pitch of the chorus part, and I had to use a different and calmer voice for the chorus part while performing,
The two members I mentioned earlier had high parts, so it was difficult for them to keep up with the difference in pitch,
Before the performance, we practiced the chorus separately from the dance and singing parts, which was quite a difficult part,
The parts were divided into A, B, C, and so on, and the parts sung by each member were completely different,
I think the atmosphere of the chorus was also different depending on the A team, B team, and so on,
I would like the audience to pay attention to these parts as well, as the "hammory" part of this song is a highlight,
The members are very conscious of this and are trying their best to make it cool, so I hope you will continue to enjoy the song.
I have the impression that BEYOND's songs are always very powerful, as are their performances, and I think this is partly due to the fact that many of their songs have a lot of "harmoly" in them,
I feel that each member of BEYOND has a very different voice, and some members are good at high notes, while others are able to play very low notes,
I think that each member has different strengths, which makes for a very cool performance,
I saw how Shimakura-san and Takase-san's high note parts were so beautiful,
I had a chance to see their live performance, and the pitch was exactly the same as what I had heard in the live performance,
I was able to feel once again the high level of BEYOND's performance.
Thank you very much.
These are the chorus recordings of BEYOND's Hi2Diamond, Rika Shimakura, and Kurumi Takase.
Hello! Project New Member Audition 2024
Celebrating its 27th year this year, Hello! Project is recruiting new members.
Every member of Hello! Project members have all experienced the same thing: auditioning.
The important thing is to have the courage to take the first step.
We will do our best to support your first step.
This time, we are holding auditions in two categories.
If you like singing, dancing, and Hello! Project.
If you are such a person, you should go to the Hello! Project category.
And for those of you who want to show off your skills and personality in addition to singing and dancing, go to the BEYONES Potential Division,
BEYONES Potential Division.
If you want to make your dream come true with us at Hello! Project and make your dreams come true.
We look forward to hearing from you.
Are you pushing yourself too hard? Relax your shoulders!
With a little luck, you'll be fine.
It's time to say goodbye to Apkami, the show brought to you by Marin Fukuda!
We've seen a lot of different videos this time.
I, Fukuda, was very impressed with the recording videos of the three of you.
I was really impressed by the recording videos of the three of you, and once again I thought that the difficulties of each group's songs were very different.
I was also able to feel that each of you has a wonderful voice through the video.
I, Eguchi, was really impressed by the making of Tsubaki Factory's music video for "Seishun Exabyte".
There were a lot of drastic effects such as dropping smart phones into the water, actually throwing them, and popping popcorn.
There were a lot of drastic effects.
I think the members themselves took a lot of risks in the way they filmed.
I was impressed by how cute the girls looked when they were really surprised.
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally get to see!
This time upcami will be with Saya Eguchi of BEYONES Subway and
and Marin Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory.
Good bye!
Next time on UPKAMI
The making of Tsubaki Factory Baby Spider music video
and
Morning Musume。24最強's recording session will be shown.
Enjoy!